♬～
(Sanada) It's like an idol photoshoot NOTE Sanada
(Imagawa) We're not just like idols.
(Ishida) My passionate feelings won't reach you like this.
(Yamanaka) Oh
It’s my first live show – I’m finally on stage too…
(Kakizaki) Anxiety? a bit…
Don't worry, the number of views on the MV is also good.
(Asai)...Hey
I wonder if there are children at live performances?
Children? why?
no? Somehow
yeah?
(Azuma) Hello, sorry.
It's just a preview, so I'll leave right away. (Manager) Huh? Mr. Yamanaka?
It’s been a while since I was in charge of Strab.
Yeah, hey, it was true.
Yamanaka-kun is an old man idol
Well, a lot of things happened.
Nice to meet you Story of Love for short... NOTE Story of Love
(All) Hello, this is Strub.
(Kotoriyu) We are the same generation as Etabo and others NOTE Takanashi
That’s right (manager) haha.
Don't make me laugh about being in the same period.
If I'm not good at it, I'll be your father's age.
(Lin) My puppy is 38 (Kagurazaka) My dad is 37
(Imagawa) We're definitely from the same generation, hahahaha.
(Odagiri) Seriously? (Higashijujo) Ukeru
Okay, let's go see the makeup room now.
Yes, do you want to go? Excuse me.
(Rin) Excuse me (Kotoriyu) Excuse me.
Well then, let's do our best together.
I feel kind of bad
However, as expected, he is in his 20s.
I never want to lose to those guys who were sparkling.
Let's fill up the seats.
Huh? ah…
That's right!
In other words, I married Asai when he was a J Leaguer.
I have a wife and a son, but due to various reasons, I am currently living separately.
So you want to invite that son to your live performance?
Dancing cool on that stage
I want to show you (Imagawa) Why are you living separately?
Well, various things...
But if you call me live
Mari, Kaoru, and Dad were all amazing.
Will you come back again?
There's no way you can call me, right?
Are we idols? That's right
No matter how you think about it, it's forbidden to gossip about idols.
But even if we say gossip, we're old men, right?
Even old men are idols
The video is growing and Eternal Boys is NOTE Eternal Boys
Now is an important time
Idols are important to me, but so is my family.
Should both be important?
This is the entertainment world where one mistake can bring you down.
I beg of you, please be aware.
Isn't it okay? I'll call you to a live performance
Kakizaki: You did it again without permission...
Because there's someone who can't take care of his only two family members.
Do you think you can take care of a lot of fans?
Hey manager
That's true, but...
(Fukuko) Oh, are you slacking off? Thank you for your hard work!
(Asai) President, my family will be at the next concert...
Oh no! Kazo?
Count...
Um, I'm counting numbers. I'm counting numbers.
I can only count the number of days left
I'm looking forward to the live performance, Asai.
Yeah yeah yeah
If that's the case, you'll have to practice and work hard.
Yes yes
Well...
Okay? Everyone, don't tell anyone
Asai's secret will be the secret of all eternal boys from today onwards.
Just call me Asai hehehehe
What are you sneaking around with?
⚟♬～
Okay, that's all for today.
Sorry, I have a meeting so I'll leave first.
(Kakizaki) I'll go too, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
(Imagawa) Ah, I'm hungry, so what's the food?
(Ishida) You said curry, is that true? How many curries?
Seafood? It's made from spices
Huh? Nikolai-san... Huh? Shallow, aren't you going home?
Ah, I'll do a little more
Ah okay Otsuotsu
Thank you for your hard work
Shall we do it some more? yes
I'll stay too. We'll do it too.
(Asai) Thank you
Where do I start? (Asai) You know, this is...
(Cell phone vibrating sound) Oh, sorry.
(cell phone vibration sound)
Kaoru, hurry up!
Yeah
(cell phone vibration sound)
Hello yes yes
Yeah yeah
Yay! Because I'm calling
Let's definitely make it a success!
♬～
I can go, I can go, just a little more (Asai) just a little more
♬(All) Doremifasofamiledo
♬ la la la la la la la la la
♬～
Ah, I don't know, look carefully
Wow!
(Kakizaki) That's nice!
♬～
Yes Sanayan Go Yes
Good evening! (Asai) Eternal boy...
(Asai/Imagawa) Ossan TV!
(Asai/Imagawa) Aiko! It's Aiko!
(All) Hahahaha
♬～
Are we old men?
Excuse me
yeah?
Yeah, this is perfect thank you
Sanayan, I'm nervous.
It's okay, Asai-san.
He's a cool guy even though he's old.
I'm sorry, I'm an old man.
(Imagawa) That's right, let's all form a circle.
That's great. (Imagawa) Mr. Yamanaka, shout out to me.
Okay
Health... (together) number one!
Safety... (together) first!
Seno... (All) Eternal boy!
Idol group Eien Shonen
We will bring energy to everyone through song and dance.
Please listen to “Eternal” NOTE Eternal
♬～
Kaoru... Mari... I'm sorry you took the trouble to come.
Dad, that's not cool.
Seriously lame
(Kaoru) Um (Mari) What? It's too late now
I know that.
But I love daddy, mommy told me too.
Kaoru: I didn't say that, hehehe.
I want you to wait just a little longer
Dad, I'll definitely invite Kaoru and Mari to a sold-out concert someday.
I'll show you two something cool again.
(Mari) Is it okay to leave it as is?
Kaoru, I'm hungry, so let's go home.
What about daddy? (Asai) Ah...
(Mari) I can't help it.Would you like to eat too, dad?
Oh, hahaha, you made a big splash, Kaoru.
let's go
(Kaoru) What do you want to eat? (Mari) What do you like?
(Asai) Shall we go to yakiniku? Hahahahaha
(Manda) It leads to a come-from-behind home run.
Shall we return the deficit?
I want to continue playing Eternal Shonen for a little while longer.